Guide to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Bureau of Administration
  - Subseries I.4: Personnel and Management Division. Country File
    - CNRRA Contract Personnel (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - CNRRA Recruitment Schedule (440) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - China Air Transport (CAT) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Colombia, Bogata Headquarters - Budget, Administrative Expenses (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Colombia, Salary Scales and Living Costs (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Costa Rica, Salary Scales and Living Costs (450) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Cuba - Havana Headquarters (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget (331> (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Liquidation, Closure, Rundown (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization (140) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing (440) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Termination Pay, Class II (452) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Cuba - Havana Mission - Salary (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Cuba, Recruitment of Cuban Doctors (442.3) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Cuba, Salary Scales Policy (450) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Cuba Mixed Commission, Organization and Administrative Expenses (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Czechoslovakia Agreement with UNRRA (251) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Czechoslovakia - Prague Headquarters (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget, 1st - 4th quarters 1946 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget, 1st - 2nd quarters 1947 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget, Administrative Expenses (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation, Closure, and Rundown (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - OrganizationPositions and Titles (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Report, Monthly Personnel (271) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales (450) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Staffing (440) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Danish Mission, Personnel Statistics (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Denmark - Copenhagen Headquarters (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st quarter 1947 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st - 3rd quarters 1946 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - OrganizationSalary Scales (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Staffing (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Dodecanese - Rhodes Headquarters (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st quarter 1947 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st - 4th quarters 1946 (331) Closure (140) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Organizational (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Dominican Republic, Salary Scales and Living Costs (450) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Ecuador, Salary Scales Policy (450) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Egypt, Recruitment of Nationals (442.3) (see retake of this folder at the end of Reel BA/14) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Egypt, Salary Scales and Living Costs Information (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - El Salvador, Salary Scales and Living Costs (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - El Shatt Camp, Organization, Reorganization, and Directives (140) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Ethiopia - Addis-Ababa Headquarters (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st - 2nd quarters 1947 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st, 3rd and 4th quarters 1946 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Classification, Reclassification (413) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure (140) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Currency (305) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Organization (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - PX (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Repatriation of Employees (464.31) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Report, Personnel 271 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales and Classification (450) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Staffing, Field Office (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - European Regional Office (ERO) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Account, Internal Audit (322) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Accounting Plan, Joint (310) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Addresses (212.4) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Addresses, Mail Forwarding for Terminated Personnel (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Allowances, Living, Policy (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Allowances, Living Subsistence and Travel while in the UK (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Allowances, Living and Travel (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Awards of Campaign Stars, Eligibility of UNRRA Personnel for (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Bonus plan (452) British Army Personnel, Employment of, Officers (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - British Army Personnel, Employment of, Officers (closed) British Army Personnel, Employment of, Ex-officers (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - British Army Officers, Secondment to IRO (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - British Civil Servants Serving with UNRRA on Approved Employment Terms (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, H.I.A.S.ter Personnel (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1943 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget 1947-48 Budget, 1947 (331) Budget, 3rd and 4th quarters 1946 (except Supply) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st and 2nd quarters 1946 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1946 (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, July 1945 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, March 1945Budget (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, Cables (331) (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, Field Service, July 1947 - August 1948 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget Information 1946 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, Supply, 1st and 2nd quarters 1947 (Box BA/11, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, Supply, 3rd and 4th quarters 1946 (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Budgets, Mission (331) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Budgets, Policy and Procedures (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Budgets, Policy, Procedures, and Budget Forecasts (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Classification (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Classification and Reclassification (413) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Closure Checklist and Minutes (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Code and Cypher (211.6) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Closure Coordination Commission, Reduction and (280) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Communications between ERO and Missions (210) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Conferences, Miscellaneous (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Currency (305) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Butler Treasury Branch (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Employees, Definition of Class I and II (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Employees, Employment of Class II (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Employees, Transfer of Class II to Class I (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Employees Compensation (459) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Employment Conditions of DPs (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Employment Conditions of DPsEmployment of Nationals of Member Nations and Others, Policy on (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Field Regulations, Personnel, Conditions of Service (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Field Regulations, Personnel, Probationary Period, Conditions of Service (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Field Service Personnel, Establishment of ERO Class I (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Field Service Personnel, Establishment of ERO Class II (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Forms, ERO (203) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Grades, Quarterly Distribution of Eqs. and ERO Employees by History (150) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Home Accounting Offices in Europe for Class I Employees (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Home Station Accounting Offices, Policy (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Home Station Accounting Offices, Policy (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Home Accounting Office (HAO) - Indians (454) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Informational Material for all UNRRA Personnel, Distribution of (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - IRO Material Prepared by UNRRA for Information to IRO (Box BA/12, Folder Side 1)
    - Leave, Annual (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, Annual Accrued (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, Sick (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, Sick Prolonged (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, Special (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, Special, Approved Saturday Mornings (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Leave, W.O.C. Service (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation, Closure (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation, Closure, Correspondence (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation Plans and Procedure (140) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation Procedure (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Liquidation, Rundown (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Loan to International Bank of Personnel (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Manual, Classification (562) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Manual, Classification (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Medical Care for Employees Working Overseas Medical Examination for UNRRA Personnel (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Medical Examinations for Personnel on Termination (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Missions Closure (140) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Missions Recruitment (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Orders, Administrative, General (240.3) (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Orders, PDMI (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Organization of ERO Budget for Personal Services, Services and Areas Department 1944 (Box BA/12, Folder Side 2)
    - Organization of ERO Budget Procedure, Vol. I (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of ERO Budget Procedure, Vol. II (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of ERO Budget Procedure, Vol. III (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of ERO Budget Procedure, Vol. IV (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of ERO Dept. of Finance and Administration, Division of Personnel (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of ERO Office of Administrative Liaison and Inspection (140) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization and Management (100) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of Personnel Establishment, Vol. I (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of Personnel Establishment, Vol. II, 1946 (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization of Personnel Establishment, Vol. III (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization, Structure, and Rundown, Dept. of Finance and Administration (140) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Organization, Closure of Units (140) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement (464) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement, Directives and Information from Headquarters, Vol. I Outplacement, Directives and Information from Headquarters, Vol. II (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement, Mrs. Hodson's Visit from Washington (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement, Policy Confidential (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement Records (Box BA/13, Folder Side 1)
    - Outplacement, References to Prospective Employees of UNRRA, Ex-UNRRA Staff (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Passports, Visas, Permits, General Policy (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel (400) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Actions in Cases of Pregnancy (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, Disposal of Files (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Division Instructions (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Division Mission Instructions (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, Europe and Middle East Missions by Citizenship, ERO Function and Class (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices by Class (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class I Classified by Grade (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class I Classified by Nationality (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class I Classified by Function (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class I Personnel Strength (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class II Classified by Function (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class II Personnel Strength (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class III by Functions and Nationality (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Missions and Field Offices, Class II (III?) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Regional Office Classified by Grade (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Regional Office Classified by Nationality (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Regional Office Classified by Organizational Unit (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Regional Office European Missions and Field Offices Classified by Sex (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, European Regional Office, Changes in Personal and Classification Status (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Establishment by Division and Grade (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Establishment, Comparison of (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Operations Staff, June-July 1945 (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Policy (401) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Posted to Headquarters, Terms of Service (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Problems, U.S., Roy Jacobson's Mission on (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Statistics Required by Washington (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Statistics, Reporting (440) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Surplus, Policy (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy (030) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy, Proposed and Manual Changes, Status of (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Position Description and Classification Specification (412) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Position Description Questionnaire, ERO and Field Missions (412) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Positions (412) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Procedure and Documentation, Class I Employees (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Promotions, DP Operations, Germany (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Promotions, Policy, Meritorious Increases (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Promotions, Policy and Procedure (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Promotions, Reclassifications in Deputy Controllers Office (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Provincial Fund (455.1) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Records, Disposal of DR Correspondence with ERO (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Records Program (212.2) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Regulations, Headquarters, Interpretation of (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Relations, Headquarters (250) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Relationships with ERO Repatriation (464.31) (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Repatriation of Class I Personnel on Termination, Travel (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Branch, Voluntary Agencies (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Repatriation, Class I Personnel Travel Vouchers, American Express (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Repatriation of Class I Personnel, Travel Branch, Cook's Travel Voucher (Box BA/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Repatriation of UNRRA Personnel, Policy (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Repatriation of Personnel, Policy (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Reports, Closure (271) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Reports, Personnel Investigation (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Report, Irving Posner (270) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Report, Personnel (271) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Report, Personnel - Key Personnel in ERO and Missions (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Report, Personnel - Missions (271) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Reports, Washington - Salary Groups and Staff Inquiries, October 1944 - May 1945 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Responsibility, Proposed Division of, between Headquarters and ERO (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Policies, Personnel Transferred to Post of Different Grade (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Policy, Retroactive Payments (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Policy, Salary Scale June 1945 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Policy, Yearly Increments (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Procedure, DP Personnel Recruited in Paris (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Scales (450) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Scales and Classification Information 1945-47 (450) Sitrep Letters (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Special Projects for Overcoming Backlogs on Temporary Increases in Work Loads (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staff Association (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staff Association, Nomination of Members to Appeals Committee (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staff Association, Residential and Social Facilities for UNRRA Staff (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staff List #5 (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Lists (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Missions (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Personnel Establishments, January-September 1948 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Personnel Establishments, June-December 1947 (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Personnel Establishments, January-May 1947 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Personnel Establishments, October-December 1946 Staffing Personnel Establishments lst-3rd quarters 1946 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Staff Pools for Unassigned Personnel (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Survey of UNRRA Salaries, Allowances and Related Items in European Region (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Terminations (464) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Termination of Class I Employees (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Termination of Continental Recruits (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer of Personnel to International Agencies (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer Policies, Personnel - Transfer to F.A.O. (Food and Agriculture Organization) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer Policies, Personnel - Transfer to I.C.E.F. (International Children's Fund) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer Policies, Personnel - Transfer to I.R.O, (International Refugee Organization) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer Policies, Personnel - Transfer to WHO (World Health Organization) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - U.S.P.H.S. (U.S. Public Health Service) Personnel, Conditions of Service (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - U.S.P.H.S. Personnel, Officers on Location to S.H.A.E.F. (Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Force) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - U.S.P.H.S. Officers to IRO, Secondment of (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Wives Serving in Same Theatre as Husbands (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Wives, Cost of Transportation to Join Husbands (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Wives, Policy on Joining Husbands, Vol. I (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Wives, Policy on Joining Husbands, Vol. II (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Wives, Policy on Joining Husbands, Vol. III (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Far East Area - Closing Mission (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Far East Missions and Offices, Instructions for Closure of (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Finland - Helsinki Headquarters (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st, 3rd, 4th quarters 1946 and 1st quarters 1947 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Organizational (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Rundown (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Staffing (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - France - A.S.P.O. Paris (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Surplus (777) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - France - Paris Headquarters (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, lst-4th quarters 1946 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure, Liquidation (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Currency (305) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Functions, Organization, Reorganization (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - History of Volunteer Societies Liaison Office (150) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Report Plans and Operations (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Assembly Center Teams (643) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Black Market Activities of UNRRA Personnel (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - DP Operations (640) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - DP Operations (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - DP Policy (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, Class I Classified by Location and Functions (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel, Class I, II, and III in Headquarters - DP Operations Central Tracing Bureau and the 3 Zones in Germany, Classified by Location (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Instructions, Miscellaneous (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy on Arrest and Trial of UNRRA Personnel, British Zone (012.4) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy on Arrest and Trial of UNRRA Personnel, French Zone (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Policy on Arrest and Trial of UNRRA Personnel, U.S. Zone (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales, Data from SHAEF (450) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Staff Association, DP Operations (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Statistical Analysis, Class I Employees in DP Operations 1945-46 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Statistical Report on DP Operation January 1947, by Paris HQ (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Terminations for Unsatisfactory Service (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Welfare Services, DPs (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Wives and Families in Germany (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany - Arolsen Headquarters (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Budget, 1st, 3rd, 4th quarters 1946 (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Classification and Reclassification (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Employment, DPs (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Organization (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Strength, DP Operation (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Positions, Description (412) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Report (271) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Rundown, Liquidation (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Salary Scales (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Staffing (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Staffing, Volunteer Agency (440) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany - Central Tracing Bureau (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Closure (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Procedure (201)) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer (140) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - War Department Records (212.2) (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Egypt, Recruitment of National (442.3) RETAKE (Box BA/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Germany Mission - Paris (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Address (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Billeting and Messing (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget, lst-4th quarters 1947 (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Classification and Reclassification (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Financial and Accounting Operations, Survey of (322) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Grades and Salaries (415) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel Report (271) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - PX Supplies (700.14) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Relations (250) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Salaries, Class II (450) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Salary Scales (450) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Personnel Establishment (440) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Staffing Volunteer Agency, Ceiling (440) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Transfer (140) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greece, Currency Information (305) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greece, Economic and Financial Developments (672) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greece, Salary Scales, Cost of Living Information (450) (Box BA/15, Folder Side 1)